The next thing I'm going to talk to you about is about having fun breathing and enjoying your dance.
When learning how to Belly-dance, make sure you just make small goals for yourself.
Make sure you don't make a big goal so that way you get discouraged.
Just make many goals for yourself, learn your move, really practice it, maybe take a week or two or however long it takes to learn that move, perfect it.
You want to enjoy this dance for years to come.
So, if it's a learning process for years, and years, and years, just enjoy it.
It's your dance and it will be uniquely yours in the end.
So just make sure you make tiny goals for yourself and don't be discouraged.
It's a dance that you should love.
And, when you love this dance, and you dance and perform for others, and it comes from your heart, from inside, the passion will show out to everybody else.
And you're dancing, whether you're a novice or a professional, it will still show.
So just learn to love yourself, love your dance, and just be patient with yourself when you're learning how to belly dance.
Another thing to do is be conscience of your breathing.
Makes sure you are breathing when you're dancing and you're learning.
This will help you keep you healthy while you're dancing.
Make sure you keep your knees bent, this will help prevent any injuries to your knees, and just enjoy yourself.